libertycoin.com 2014-11-22

# Liberty Coin | Terms: Privacy

This privacy policy lets you know what information we collect, how we may share that information, and your choices regarding the sharing of your information.

HIGHLIGHTS

**Personal Information:**

We may collect personal information such as your contact, billing and shipping information. We may also collect demographic information.

We collect information regarding your interactions with our Web sites using cookies or clickstream technology.

We may obtain additional personal and non-personal information from third party providers.

YOUR CHOICES

**You may choose to:**

Stop receiving e-mail, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications.

Update and correct your personal information.

USES OF INFORMATION

Liberty Coin, LLC does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.

We use information about you to fulfill your requests, administer various programs, provide services, and for other business purposes.

Your personal information may be shared with current or future Liberty Coin, LLC entities or subsidiaries. We may also use the information you provide to send you marketing communications.

In limited circumstances, Liberty Coin, LLC may need to share your information with certain third parties to perform services on our behalf.

IMPORTANT INFORMATION

Liberty Coin, LLC does not knowingly collect information online from children under 13.

Liberty Coin, LLC values our relationship with our customers and we are committed to responsible information-handling practices. View our entire Privacy Policy.

HOW TO CONTACT US

**If you have questions about Liberty Coin, LLC Privacy Policy, contact us by:**

**Phone:** 1-800-400-0824

**Regular mail:**  
Liberty Coin, LLC  
Attn: Customer Care/Privacy  
2201 E. Willow Street, Suite AA  
Signal Hill, CA 90755
